A Guide to the Virginia Genealogical Society Subject Files, 1960-1979
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Virginia Genealogical Society Subject Files, 1960-1979
The Library of Virginia
34361
2.45 cu. ft. (3 boxes)
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of the Virginia Genealogical Society, 1993.
Biographical Information
The Virginia Genealogical Society was organized in 1960 in Richmond, Virginia. Its aims were to promote Virginia genealogical research, especially in those counties that had suffered a substantial loss of records. The society publishes a quarterly and a newsletter.
Scope and Content
This collection consists of a collection of office subject files collected over the years by the society. They are primarily genealogical in nature and are arranged alphabetically. There are some cemetery and census transcriptions as well as newsletters and Bible records.
Contents List
- Correspondence, 1970-1979. (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Objectives, Letters to the President, 1974-1979. (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Publication Announcements. (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Alabama Census records, 1850, Blount County. (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Alabama Census records, 1850, Monroe County. (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Alabama Marriage records, Tallapoosa County, 1835-1845. (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Alabama Newspaper Extracts. (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Alabama Tombstones - Giving Virginia as Birthplace. (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Allen family. (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Ballard family. (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Bagby family. (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Ballew family. (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Barks family. (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Barnes family. (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Bewley family. (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Blakemore family. (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Boggs family. (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Bowen family. (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Brown family. (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Bruce family of Halifax County. (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Burnett family. (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Burton family. (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Calhoun family. (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Carlton, Cardwell, and Richeson families. (Box 1, Folder 24)
- California Cemeteries. (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Chamberlain family. (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Chesterfield County, VA, Bibliography. (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Christmas family. (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Clopton family. (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Counts family of Loudoun and Fairfax Counties. (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Cowne family. (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Culpeper County, VA, Cemetery. (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Daugherty family. (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Davenport family of Charlotte County. (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Davis family of Pittsylvania and Henry Counties. (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Day family. (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Deaton family. (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Dew, Thomas R. to John Millington, Letter, 1837. (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Emmerson family of Pittsylvania County. (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Ewing family. (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Fairfax Genealogical Society. (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Fearn family. (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Federation of Genealogical Societies. (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Ferguson family. (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Fitzgerald family. (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Flippin family of Chesterfield County. (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Foster family of Charlotte and Northumberland Counties. (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Fountain family Bible records. (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Fowler family. (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Gest/Guest family. (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Gillam family. (Box 1, Folder 51-52)
- Goins family of Wythe County. (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Goodpasture family. (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Grayson family. (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Hanby family of Patrick County. (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Hash family. (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Hawse family. (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Henrico County. (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Higdon family. (Box 1, Folder 60)
- Hillard family. (Box 1, Folder 61)
- Hogg family of Culpeper County. (Box 1, Folder 62)
- Hyde-Blackwell families Bible records. (Box 1, Folder 63)
- Illinois, Rock Island Cemetery. (Box 2, Folder 64)
- Isaacs family Bible record. (Box 2, Folder 65)
- Jenkins family. (Box 2, Folder 66)
- Key family. (Box 2, Folder 67)
- Lawson family. (Box 2, Folder 68)
- Lilly family. (Box 2, Folder 69)
- Lipscomb family. (Box 2, Folder 70)
- Long-Herndon families. (Box 2, Folder 71)
- Mercer family of Frederick County. (Box 2, Folder 72)
- Meriwether family. (Box 2, Folder 73-74)
- Mulkey family. (Box 2, Folder 75-80)
- Nesbitt/Nisbet family. (Box 2, Folder 81)
- Nichols family. (Box 2, Folder 82)
- Nickell family of Augusta County. (Box 2, Folder 83)
- Nicolson family. (Box 2, Folder 84)
- Nottoway County. (Box 2, Folder 85)
- Old Concord Presbyterian Church, Church register, 1826-1878. (Box 2, Folder 86)
- Osborne family of Charlotte County, VA and Floyd County, KY. (Box 2, Folder 87)
- Owens family. (Box 2, Folder 88)
- Pendleton County, WVA, Tax list, 1797. (Box 2, Folder 89)
- Phillips family of Mecklenburg, Amherst, and Nelson Counties - Bible record. (Box 2, Folder 90)
- Revolutionary soldiers who lived in both VA and AL. (Box 2, Folder 91)
- Rockett family. (Box 2, Folder 92)
- Royston family of Gloucester County. (Box 2, Folder 93)
- Russell family. (Box 2, Folder 94)
- Sallee family. (Box 2, Folder 95)
- Shackelford family. (Box 2, Folder 96)
- Simmons family. (Box 2, Folder 97)
- Sly family of Fairfax County. (Box 2, Folder 98)
- Jesse Smith family cemetery records. (Box 2, Folder 99)
- Smith family of Dinwiddie County. (Box 2, Folder 100)
- Stafford County, Cemetery records. (Box 2, Folder 101)
- Stafford County, Cemetery records, Norman and Towson families. (Box 2, Folder 102)
- Stanley and Bassett families of Henry County. (Box 2, Folder 103)
- Stovall family. (Box 2, Folder 104)
- Stover family. (Box 2, Folder 105)
- Strickland family. (Box 2, Folder 106)
- Texas Cemetery records, Monroe County. (Box 3, Folder 107)
- Thomason family. (Box 3, Folder 108)
- Thruston family. (Box 3, Folder 109)
- Travis family. (Box 3, Folder 110)
- Truman family. (Box 3, Folder 111)
- Tull family. (Box 3, Folder 112)
- United Daughters of the Confederacy, Manassas Chapter. (Box 3, Folder 113)
- Vanlandingham family of Northumberland County. (Box 3, Folder 114)
- Virginia Marriages, Rev. John Cameron's Register. (Box 3, Folder 115)
- Wall family of Rowan County, NC. (Box 3, Folder 116)
- Washington family. (Box 3, Folder 117)
- White family. (Box 3, Folder 118)
- Williams family. (Box 3, Folder 119)